http://hospitality.fiu.edu/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy – Chaplin School of Hospitality & Tourism Management
Skip to content
Transforming hospitality and tourism... one learner at a time, for a lifetime.
FacebookTwitterYouTubeLinkedInInstagram
Search for:
Search for:
Main MenuABOUTAPPLY CloseSTEPS TO APPLYHow to Apply / UndergraduateHow to Apply / GraduateUNDERGRADUATEDeadlinesApplication StatusInternational ApplicantsSend TranscriptsApplyGRADUATEDeadlinesApplication StatusInternational ApplicantsApply: Master’sApply: DoctoralRESOURCESPaying for SchoolCalculate CostsCost of AttendanceFinancial AidInternational Studentand Scholar ServicesMilitary/Veterans CloseUNDERGRADUATE CloseBACHELOR OF SCIENCE PROGRAMSB.S. in Hospitality ManagementCombined Bachelor of Science andMaster of Science (4+1) ProgramMinorsFood & Beverage Science ResearchCERTIFICATE PROGRAMSInternet of Things IoT in HospitalityQUICK LINKSCanvasmyFIUPanthermailHospitality ManagementCourse Schedule CloseGRADUATE CloseMASTER OF SCIENCEM.S. in HospitalityManagement (non-thesis)M.S. in HospitalityManagement (thesis)Master of Science in HospitalityManagement – Specialization inRevenue ManagementM.S. in HospitalityManagement – Specialization inHospitality Real Estate DevelopmentDOCTORAL PROGRAMSEd.D. in Adult Education & HumanResource DevelopmentQUICK LINKSHospitality ManagementCourse Schedule CloseONLINE CloseUNDERGRADUATEB.S. in Hospitality ManagementGRADUATEMaster of Science in Hospitality ManagementMaster of Science in HospitalityManagement – Specialization inRevenue ManagementM.S. in HospitalityManagement – Specialization inHospitality Real Estate DevelopmentM.S. in HospitalityManagement with Specialization inMega Events CloseCHINACAREERFACULTYALUMNIGIVING
Search for:
Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyAdministrator2017-01-24T13:35:30-05:00
Thank you for visiting the Florida International University (FIU) Chaplin School of Hospitality & Management & Tourism Management website. Your privacy is very important to us. Simply stated, we do not collect personal information about you when you visit the Chaplin School website unless you choose to make such information available to us.
When you visit the Chaplin School site, the University’s web server automatically recognizes only the Internet domain and IP address from which you accessed the site. This information does not result in the identification of your personal e-mail address or other personal information.
Anonymous information regarding the date, time, and pages visited while you are on the site is collected to improve user experience. Your personal information is not identified or shared with other organizations.
If you choose to share personal information with us, such as by subscribing to an electronic newsletter, sending a message, or filling out an electronic form with personal information, the information will be saved for a designated period of time in order to comply with the State of Florida’s archiving policies. However, information will not be disclosed to third parties or other government agencies, unless required by state or federal law. Please note that Florida’s public records law requires that all information received in connection with state business including e-mail addresses, be made available to anyone upon request, unless the information is subject to a specific statutory exemption. If you do not want your e-mail address disclosed as a public record, please contact the University via telephone or by U.S. mail.
If you have other questions about this Privacy Policy, or have suggestions on how it may be improved, please feel free to e-mail us at hospitality@fiu.edu or contact us by telephone at 305.919.4500.
This statement constitutes the Privacy Policy for the Chaplin School website only. Please note that while FIU respects individual privacy, websites of other units within FIU may have different privacy practices.
The Chaplin School website may contain links to external websites over which it has no responsibility or control for its content. Therefore, it is your responsibility to read and agree to any privacy policies and terms of use that may be posted on external websites you navigate to or visit.
Search for:
Archives
June 2020
April 2020
March 2020
February 2020
December 2019
November 2019
October 2019
ABOUT THE CHAPLIN SCHOOL
FIU's Chaplin School of Hospitality & Tourism Management offers bachelor's and master's degree concentrations in key areas in the industry.
Why Chaplin?
Mission,
Vision & Accreditation
Meet the Dean
Faculty and Staff Directory
Fast Facts
Corporate Partnerships
NEED HELP?
Quick Links Hospitality Academic Advisors
Academic and Student Resources
FAQs
Scholarships
VISIT
Visit the Chaplin School
FIU Campus Maps
Get Directions
CONTACT US
Request Program Information Chaplin School of Hospitality & Tourism Management 3000 N.E. 151st Street North Miami, FL 33181-3000 Tel: 305.919.4500 Fax: 305.919.4555 E-mail: hospitality@fiu.edu
ACCREDITED
Employment | In the Media | Privacy Policy | Feedback
© 2020 Florida International University Chaplin School of Hospitality & Tourism Management
FacebookTwitterYouTubeLinkedInInstagram
Go to Top
